bforex.com 2017-02-01

# Privacy Policy

Bforex respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take great pride in maintaining the privacy and therefore the loyalty of each individual client, by providing the required security. The provisions of this notice apply to both former and current customers. 

### 1\. Personal Information

In order to provide you with the very best service, when you apply to become a bforex customer or open a live account, we will ask you for personal information. This information will assist us in evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, keeping you informed about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing you with a better customer experience.

### 2\. Required Information May Include:

**Application Information – full name, address, birth date, identity − social security number, occupation, assets and income.**

Transaction Information – Information about your transactions with us and/or our affiliates, and records of past communications. These may include your account balances, trading activity, past inquiries and our responses.

Verification Information – This may be required to verify your identity, and may include passport or driver’s license.

Note: Anti-Money Laundering ("AML") regulations and the USA Patriot Act requires financial institutions to collect information and take action where necessary, in order to verify a customer’s identity.

Note: bforex does not intentionally collect information from persons under thirteen years of age. 

### 3\. The Use of Cookies

We use a technology called "cookies", which enables us to provide you with a better experience in using our website by sending small text files from our servers to your computer. These cookies do not track your private information. 

### 4\. Sharing Information:

a. Affiliates  
We may share some or all of the personal information described above with our affiliates in order to service client accounts or inform clients of new products and services. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us, as well as companies which have an ownership interest in our company. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information in the same manner and to the same extent as bforex, and in accordance with this privacy policy.

b. Third Parties  
Bforex does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this privacy policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with bforex. These companies may include those that provide professional, legal or accounting services to bforex. Non-affiliate companies that assist bforex in providing services are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it. In addition, they are obligated to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes dictated by bforex.

Bforex may disclose a customer’s personal information to a third party in order to fulfill their instructions or pursuant to express consent. It is important to us that you know that bforex will not sell your personal information.

c. Regulators  
Bforex may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations. This may include disclosing personal information in order to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies, as may be necessary to protect our property or rights.

d. Merger or Bankruptcy  
Bforex is obliged to maintain customer information according to its incorporation laws. In the event of a merger, the information will merge along with the company. In the event of bankruptcy, different legal statuses shall apply in accordance with its incorporation laws and its recordkeeping requirements.

e. Payment Information  
bforex does not keep, in any form, customer payment information. 

### 5\. Failure to Provide Personal Information

You have a choice to supply any or all of the personal information required. However, missing information may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account and /or to provide you with our services.

### 6\. Opt Out   

Should you choose to have your name and personal data removed from our database, you can do so by sending an email to [privacy@bforex.com](mailto:privacy@bforex.com)

### 7\. Amendments   

Any amendments to our privacy policy that affect the personal information of users collected on our website will be notified to the users, within a reasonable time, via email. Users will have a choice whether or not we use the information in a different manner. Any amendments made by us that do not affect personal information will be posted on our website.

### 8\. Mailing Information

Whether you wish to talk to us about our privacy policy or any other issue, the professional team at bforex is available to assist you 24/7. Please feel free to contact us via e-mail, phone, fax and mailing address. You can also use our chat facility to IM a customer service representative.

Mailing Address:

5 Ebury Bridge Road  
London  
SW1W SQX  
United Kingdom

  * Fax: +44 207 806 8094
  * Tel: +44 203 514 0458
  * E-mail: [support.en@bforex.com](mailto:support.en@bforex.com)

This Privacy Policy is in effect from 11.06.2009.
